

Muhammad Aldi Joko Satria Perdana

Mayjend Sutoyo S, Banjarmasin Tengah, Banjarmasin City, South Borneo, 70117 maldijokosp@gmail.com | 08981187320

SUMMARY

Joko is who like to learn new things and try my best for all my job based on my experience. He is received the bachelor and certification from the University of Muhammadiyah Yogyakarta and NIIT India (National Institute of Information Technology Academy India).

EDUCATION

Universitas Muhammadiyah Yogyakarta (UMY)
Bachelor's Degree Information Technology – GPA 3.65/4.00
Sep 2015 – Oct 2019

National Institute of Information Technology Academy India (NIIT)
PNIIT Software Engineering

Sep 2015 – Oct 2019

EXPERIENCES

Volantis Technology - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

April 2022 – Present

Frontend Developer

- Developing Website for project Pascasarjana using svelte framework
- Maintenance website Gocuit

RS Bhayangkara Banjarmasin – Banjarmasin, Indonesia

Jan 2021 – Mar 2022

IT Support

- Maintenance Hardware like computer and laptop in RS Bhayangkara.
- Maintenance and Troubleshooting Internet network RS Bhayangkara.
- Install and Update Application in RS Bhayangkara

PT Infosys Solusi Terpadu- Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Apr 2020 – Nov 2020

Frontend Developer

- Developing CIMB Niaga Mobile Banking for payment online using javascript and tool kony visualizer.
- Developing web application for internal employee CIMB Niaga using javascript and ReactJS
- Integration Application using API with Postman.

PT Indonesia Indicator – Jakarta, Indonesia

Jan 2020 – Mar 2020

Backend Developer

• Data retrieval using Java Springboot and mongodb database

SKILLS, INTERESTS, AND LANGUAGES

- Skills Java, Java Script, HTML, CSS, ReactJS, Svelte.
- Interest Front End Developer, Website Development.
- Languages –Indonesian (*native*) and English (*fluent*)